Through the AI text generator, you can enter keywords to generate multiple images and learn fabric text from them.
Go to the Fabric Type window and select a fabric type.
In the Fabric Type property, click the AI Text Generator button next to the default, and select the appropriate plant type.
In the Pattern Type, select the type of text.
Enter keywords.
Entering the appropriate keywords is more effective than using long sentences.
Click the Create button to view the generated images in the preview window.
When entering keywords, enter the images you want to be created in English with more precision.
The generated images will be stored in the history record.
The generated images are only temporarily previewed before you click on the application.
Click Create again to create more other images.
The previously generated images will be stored as historical records.
Before Marvelous Designer closes, you can always visit these historical records.
Enter keywords similar to the AI Text Generator to generate multiple random images as a sticker.
Use the sticker 2D version tool to load any sticker file to the clothing version.
In the Fabric Type window, click the AI Text Generator button next to the default.
Select the pattern type to set whether to use transparent background.
Enter keywords.
Click the Create button.
The generated stickers can be seen in the history record.
Click Create again to generate more sticker images.
Click the App button.
The selected image will be applied as a sticker.
You can set the repeat type in the property editor to set the sticker.
Use the Adjust Sticker tool.
You can place, rotate, and slide the sticker.
Now you can automatically generate PBR stickers based on the printed text and sticker photos.
First, use the sticker 2D tool to add a sticker to the cloth.
Select Sticker by adjusting the Sticker tool.
In the property editor, click the PBR sticker button next to the sticker channel.
Click Create.
In this example, you can see that the hair line sticker has been automatically generated.
You can adjust the intensity of the hair line sticker below to get a more suitable effect.
The generated PBR sticker will automatically be stored in the AppData folder in your computer.
Click on the sticker shortcut to see the picture in the path.
Click on the PBR sticker to create a hair line sticker for the hair line sticker.
This feature can be used to create PBR stickers for fabric, buttons, eyes, stickers, accessories, lines, and hair.
Now you can manage the accessories style and type in the independent accessory window.
Change the window type to Trim.
You can download the OBJ-FBX file.
In this way, the accessory window will automatically generate the corresponding accessory type.
If you need to add your file to an accessory type, please click the Add button or drag an accessory to the accessory window.
Drag the accessory from the accessory window to the 3D space to add it to the 3D window.
You can attach it to the outfit with a glue tool.
Select the accessory in the 3D window.
Click on the App button next to the accessory type to change the accessory style.
When you modify an accessory type attribute, all accessories that apply this type will be modified at the same time.
You can choose to open the Save option in the accessory type attribute to load or save the accessory style.
The animation data of the costume and the virtual model can be imported and exported through the USB file format.
Please go to the main menu and import the USB file.
Then select the USB file.
The accessory window is similar to other file formats.
You can set the type of download and the type of object.
And set the unit and shrink according to your needs.
Then you can adjust the axis conversion according to your needs.
You can compare the files after downloading to confirm whether the axis conversion setting is correct.
Click Confirm and download the USB file.
If there is no USB layer window in the workspace, a window will automatically pop up.
You can see the Prime path of the inserted USB file.
Because the file has Google animation,
it will automatically form an animation bar in the animation window.
You can create a costume first and then record the animation.
The animation of the costume file can be exported to the USB file.
Please confirm that the USB file you exported is also set to the Authoring layer.
Set the Prime path of the grid and material.
In the options below, please select the Cache animation option.
Click Confirm and view the layer editor.
The grid and material will be saved in the set Prime path.
Because the version of the Cache animation will be exported as a grid,
there is no other independent animation type Prime.
If you need to export the costume and virtual model at the same time,
please select the virtual model first and then select the costume version.
In the export option, if your virtual model animation uses the joint animation,
please ensure that the joint animation and the cache animation are selected at the same time.
In the display menu bar of the 2D window,
please select the layer option to display the layers of each version.
Click the 2D star icon to open the layer layer function in the display menu.
The layer value will be displayed on the version.
The version with the same layer will be displayed in the same color.
From layer 1 to layer 23, they are all different colors.
Then from layer 24, repeat the cycle.
The color of the number of layers is the same as its relative number of layers.
Click the display layer layer function again to turn it off.
When you switch to the 2D layer rendering style,
it will automatically turn off the display layer layer function.
In the 2D information display tab,
you can turn on the display tab function.
Click the icon on the tab to change the tab unit.
As the mouse rolls,
the tab will automatically be released.
Click and drag the cross point of the left upper left corner of the tab.
As the mouse moves,
you can set the round point of the tab.
When you release the mouse,
the round point of the tab will be set as the cross point of the cross line.
You need to reset the round point of the tab.
On the blank square on the left upper left corner,
click the left mouse button or the right mouse button.
Click and drag the level or value of the tab to create a reference line.
When a reference line approaches the left upper left corner,
the point on the outside of the tab will be copied to the point.
Press the Ctrl key and drag the level or value of the tab
to create a reference line with the opposite axis.
When the tab is moved,
the points on the tab will also be copied to the reference line.
On the right of the reference line,
there are relevant function options.
You can delete the single reference line or the full reference line.
Lock one or more reference lines.
Or create more reference lines through the reference line shortcut function.
Enter the number of extensions in the window.
You can set different shortcuts between reference lines.
You can also choose to create a reference line on the other side,
or create one along both sides.
When you select to apply all the extensions,
you will create a reference line with multiple extensions.
The reference line function can run independently of the display icon function.
You can go to the 2D information and select the display or hidden reference line
in the drop-down menu.
The UV fill algorithm has been optimized.
Now you can get a higher quality result.
Select the UV shell and then click the UV fill button.
A new option has been added, Accuracy.
The larger the value, the more accurate it is when calculating the shape of the UV shell.
In addition, we have added a new option to optimize the layout.
When the optimization layout is closed,
the UV shell will be placed from large to small once.
However, when the optimization layout is selected,
the background will test a large number of sequences to find a better layout method,
which is the least open space.
The optimization layout function will reduce the layout speed.
However, unless there is a special situation,
it is recommended that you keep the optimization layout.
Now you can set the UV fill fill pixel or set it as infinite fill
in the UV editor window.
In the UV editor window,
click on the UV fill pixel and set the storage path.
Then you can set the UV shell fill pixel.
Select the type of texture you want to export,
then click Save.
When setting too large a fill value,
UV fill fill may affect other UV shells.
You can set infinite fill to avoid this problem.
You can now display or hide the color hint
that applies to the special state on the panel or grid.
When the panel applies the function of freezing, shape solidification,
hardening, and layer,
you can hide the color hint by clicking the right button in the 3D background to display the hidden color function.
After clicking the display hidden color menu,
you can select the corresponding menu according to your needs.
In the same right button menu,
you can select display all,
and display all the color hints.
This function is also applicable to the color hint in the special state on the grid.
The color hint can be hidden in the panel,
detail, shape solidification,
and color hardening.
Now we support the panel position function,
which is convenient to adjust the hand position separately.
You can use the edge pose and pose files
to apply the hand position to the virtual model.
You can open a female VR or male VR virtual model,
and then enter a position file.
In the pop-up window,
in the panel position option,
select both hands or left and right hands
to load the hand position separately.
When loading the position,
it will automatically start the simulation,
and the hand position will gradually change.
Edge pose is a file format,
it only stores the data of the hand position.
You can separate the different hand positions for left and right hands.
When there are multiple virtual models at the same time,
please remember to select the corresponding virtual model.
Thank you for watching,
see you in the next video.